<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JavaScript on Code by Ember Zhang</title>
    <link>https://emberlzhang.github.io/tags/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JavaScript on Code by Ember Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2024 Ember Zhang</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://emberlzhang.github.io/tags/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons and Portals</title>
      <link>https://emberlzhang.github.io/post/dungeons-portals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://emberlzhang.github.io/post/dungeons-portals/</guid>
      <description>Description The Dungeons &amp;amp; Portals Game is a platformer game developed in vanilla JavaScript within a Flask application.&#xA;Link: https://dungeons-and-portals.onrender.com&#xA;Code: https://github.com/emberlzhang/task_dungeon-portals-game&#xA;Purpose The Dungeons &amp;amp; Portals Game was designed for the Center for Computational Psychiatry at Mount Sinai Hospital to differentiate between clinical populations with behavioral compulsions and healthy control (HC) populations.&#xA;Overview Each round of the game, the player chooses a dungeon to enter, then tries to escape the dungeon using the fewest number of portal teleportations possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rose Garden Game</title>
      <link>https://emberlzhang.github.io/post/rose-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://emberlzhang.github.io/post/rose-garden/</guid>
      <description>Description The Rose Garden Game is a game developed in React.JS and JavaScript.&#xA;Code: https://github.com/emberlzhang/task_rose-garden_two-step&#xA;Purpose The Rose Garden game was designed for the Center for Computational Psychiatry at Mount Sinai Hospital to differentiate between clinical populations with obsessive compulsive disorder (OCD) and healthy control (HC) populations. The task is inspired by the classic &amp;ldquo;two-stage&amp;rdquo; task paradigm in cognitive behavioral research.&#xA;Gameplay The player plays rounds of two repeating choices followed in succession:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spaceships and Aliens</title>
      <link>https://emberlzhang.github.io/post/spaceships-aliens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://emberlzhang.github.io/post/spaceships-aliens/</guid>
      <description>Description The Spaceships and Aliens Game is a game developed in JavaScript (TypeScript).&#xA;Link: https://spaceships-aliens.vercel.app&#xA;Code: https://github.com/emberlzhang/task_spaceships-aliens_twostep&#xA;Purpose The Spaceships and Aliens game is an online behavioral task designed for the Center for Computational Psychiatry at Mount Sinai Hospital to differentiate between clinical populations with obsessive compulsive disorder (OCD) and healthy control (HC) populations. The task is inspired by the classic &amp;ldquo;two-stage&amp;rdquo; task paradigm in cognitive behavioral research.&#xA;Gameplay Overview The player plays rounds of two repeating choices followed in succession:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fish Task &amp; API Integration (Yale School of Medicine)</title>
      <link>https://emberlzhang.github.io/post/yale-fish-task/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://emberlzhang.github.io/post/yale-fish-task/</guid>
      <description>Description The Fishing Task is a game developed in JavaScript and Node.JS, and modelled upon an original version in PsychoJS. Additionally, API integrations with external services were done in AWS Lamdba.&#xA;Purpose The Fishing Task is an online behavioral task developed for the Powers Lab at Yale Medical School to use on clinical and healthy populations during clinical studies on ketamine, a psychoactive used for pain relief, anxiety and mood disorders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Shape Task (Desrochers Lab - Brown University)</title>
      <link>https://emberlzhang.github.io/post/color-shape-task/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://emberlzhang.github.io/post/color-shape-task/</guid>
      <description>Description The Color Shape Task is an online web application written in JavaScript and JSPsych, a JavaScript framework made for psychology, neuroscience, and cognitive science researchers. The application back-end was built in a Flask-inspired research-specific framework called Psiturk, and setup to integrate with Amazon Mechanical Turk, a recruitment platform used for online research studies. Docker was used for a streamlined and stable deployment.&#xA;Code: https://github.com/DesrochersLab/seq1_online_app&#xA;Purpose The Color Shape Task is an online behavioral task developed for the Desrochers Lab of the Neuroscience department at Brown University to use on healthy populations during research studies on higher level sequential processing, a cognitive process involving the dorsolateral prefrontal cortex, potentially implicating conditions like obsessive compulsive disorder.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
