<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JavaScript on Ember Zhang [Code]</title>
    <link>https://emberlzhang.github.io/tags/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JavaScript on Ember Zhang [Code]</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2024 Ember Zhang</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://emberlzhang.github.io/tags/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons and Portals | Mount Sinai Hospital</title>
      <link>https://emberlzhang.github.io/portfolio/dungeons-portals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://emberlzhang.github.io/portfolio/dungeons-portals/</guid>
      <description>Description The Dungeons &amp;amp; Portals Game is a platformer game developed in vanilla JavaScript within a Flask application.&#xA;Link: https://dungeons-and-portals.onrender.com&#xA;Code: https://github.com/emberlzhang/task_dungeon-portals-game&#xA;Purpose The Dungeons &amp;amp; Portals Game was designed for the Center for Computational Psychiatry at Mount Sinai Hospital to differentiate between clinical populations with behavioral compulsions and healthy control (HC) populations.&#xA;Overview Each round of the game, the player chooses a dungeon to enter, then tries to escape the dungeon using the fewest number of portal teleportations possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rose Garden Game | Mount Sinai Hospital</title>
      <link>https://emberlzhang.github.io/portfolio/rose-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://emberlzhang.github.io/portfolio/rose-garden/</guid>
      <description>Description The Rose Garden Game is a game developed in React.JS and JavaScript.&#xA;Code: https://github.com/emberlzhang/task_rose-garden_two-step&#xA;Purpose The Rose Garden game was designed for the Center for Computational Psychiatry at Mount Sinai Hospital to differentiate between clinical populations with obsessive compulsive disorder (OCD) and healthy control (HC) populations. The task is inspired by the classic &amp;ldquo;two-stage&amp;rdquo; task paradigm in cognitive behavioral research.&#xA;Gameplay The player plays rounds of two repeating choices followed in succession:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spaceships and Aliens | Mount Sinai Hospital</title>
      <link>https://emberlzhang.github.io/portfolio/spaceships-aliens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://emberlzhang.github.io/portfolio/spaceships-aliens/</guid>
      <description>Description The Spaceships and Aliens Game is a game developed in JavaScript (TypeScript).&#xA;Link: https://spaceships-aliens.vercel.app&#xA;Code: https://github.com/emberlzhang/task_spaceships-aliens_twostep&#xA;Purpose The Spaceships and Aliens game is an online behavioral task designed for the Center for Computational Psychiatry at Mount Sinai Hospital to differentiate between clinical populations with obsessive compulsive disorder (OCD) and healthy control (HC) populations. The task is inspired by the classic &amp;ldquo;two-stage&amp;rdquo; task paradigm in cognitive behavioral research.&#xA;Gameplay Overview The player plays rounds of two repeating choices followed in succession:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
